Guide to the Walter E. Fauntroy papers, 1941-1990 MS2070
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Affiliations and organization files, 1940-1989; MS2070 Series 2; 6 Linear feet
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Program. 20th Anniversary March On Washington, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1963: Speech, 20th Anniversary March On Washington, Circa 1983 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1988: Correspondence, David Clarke, 1988 August 29 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1988: Correspondence, The Great March On Washington (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1988: Flyers. The Great March On Washington (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1988: Meeting Files, The Great March On Washington (Box 30, Folder 43)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1988: News Releases, The Great March On Washington (Box 30, Folder 44)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1988: Program, Supplement 25th Anniversary March on Washington (Box 30, Folder 45)
  - Southern Christian Leadership Conference; March on Washington 1988: Statements, The Great March On Washington (Box 30, Folder 46)
- Campaign files, 1970-1990; MS2070 Series 3; 1.5 Linear feet
  Materials in this series include committee agendas, bumper stickers, correspondence, clippings, endorsements, flyers, pamphlets, press releases, proposals, statements and workshop files in support of Fauntroy's congressional campaigns in the 1970s and 1980s, committee agendas, campaign T-shirts, endorsements, and statements supporting Fauntroy's 1990 campaign for mayor of the District of Columbia. This material covers the time period 1970-90.
  This materials relates to Fauntroy's congressional and mayoral campaigns.
  - Congressional campaign file: Bumper Sticker 1974 Campaign (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Congressional campaign file: Brochures, Campaign 1988 Re-election (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Congressional campaign file: Clippings, Congressional Campaign, 1972-1984 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Congressional campaign file: Correspondence, Constituents, 1970 October 22 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Congressional campaign file: Correspondence, Campaign Meeting, 1970 November 11 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Congressional campaign file: Correspondence, Campaign 71', 1971 March 25-May 01 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Congressional campaign file: Correspondence, Campaign Contributions, 1971 April 22 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Congressional campaign file: Correspondence, Endorsement for Fauntroy, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Congressional campaign file: Correspondence 1974 Campaign (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Congressional campaign file: Correspondence, Senate Chairmanship, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Congressional campaign file: Correspondence, Louis Stokes, undated (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Congressional campaign file: Flyer 1974 Campaign (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Congressional campaign file: Flyer, Re-Elect Fauntroy, Circa 1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Congressional campaign file: Manual, Precinct Cap Workshop 1974 Campaign, 1974 August 13 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Congressional campaign file: Meeting Files, Campaign 71', 1970 November 12 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Congressional campaign file: Meeting Files 1974 Campaign, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Congressional campaign file: Meeting Files, Democratic Central Committee and Caucus of United Democratic Elected Officials, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Congressional campaign file: Meeting File, Petition 1982 Campaign, 1982 May 15 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Congressional campaign file: Meeting Files, Campaign Committee 1982 Campaign (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Congressional campaign file: Meeting Files, Campaign Committee, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Congressional campaign file: Meeting Files, Campaign Committee, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Congressional campaign file: News Release, Endorsement for Congress, 1970 November 07 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Congressional campaign file: News Release, The Faith Of Our For Fathers, 1970 November 07 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Congressional campaign file: News Releases 1974 Campaign (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Congressional campaign file: Pamphlet, Re-Election to Congress, 1984-1988 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Congressional campaign file: Press Kit 1982 Campaign, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Congressional campaign file: Proposal, Toward a Washington Agenda, undated (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Congressional campaign file: Report 1974 Campaign Survey Report (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Congressional campaign file: Statement, Seeking Congressional Office, 1970 October 16 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Congressional campaign file: Statement, Congressional Candidacy, 1971 January 07 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Congressional campaign file: Statements, 1974 Campaign Endorsements (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Congressional campaign file: Statements, 1974 Campaign (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Congressional campaign file: Subject File 1984 Re-Election Campaign Open House (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Congressional campaign file: Transcript, Robert Hooks, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: T-shirt 1990 Mayoral Campaign (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: T-shirt 1990 Mayoral Campaign (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Articles 1990 Mayoral Campaign (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Clippings 1990 Mayoral Campaign (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Correspondence, Requesting Support (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Correspondence 1990 Mayoral Campaign, 1990 March 05 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Correspondence, Reply to Invitations and Statements, 1990 August (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Correspondence, by Staff, 1990 August 14-16 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Correspondence, Invitation to Speak, 1990 April 05 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Correspondence, Washington View Magazine (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Flyers, Elect Fauntroy For Mayor (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Flyers, Committee and Support Organizations (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Meeting Files 1990 Mayoral Campaign (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Agenda 1990 Mayoral Campaign (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Agenda, Mayoral Campaign 1990 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Voter Registration Petition and Canvassing Workshop Material (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: News Releases 1990 Mayoral Campaign (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Remarks, Women's National Democratic Club, 1990 April 18 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Speech, "Nursing In the Nineties", 1990 May 18 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Statements 1990 Mayoral Campaign, 1990 March-August (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Statement, Labor Committee (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - 1990 Mayoral campaign file: Statement, Mayoral Platform Issues (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Congressional committee files, 1819-1989; MS2070 Series 4; 12 Linear feet
  This series contains clippings, news releases, petitions, booklets, correspondence, proclamations, reports, testimonies and announcements. These materials date from 1819-1989 with the bulk covering 1971-89. These records relate to congressional committee papers generated during Fauntroy's twenty-year career in the United States Congress. These records cover such subjects as Select Committees on Assassination and Narcotics Abuse and Control. D.C. Statehood Coalition, D.C. Home Rule, Committee on Banking Finance and Urban Affairs, Congressional Black Caucus, and Congressional Caucus on Women.
  - Select committee file: Clippings, House Assassination Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Select committee file: Clippings, House Assassination Committee, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Select committee file: Statement, Anti-Drug Abuse, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Select committee file: Statement, Drug Problem and Housing, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Select committee file: Statement, Drugs and Violence, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Select committee file: Statement, Response to Drug Czar Bennett's Plan for D.C., 1989 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Select committee file: Statement, King Assassination, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Select committee file: Briefing Book, Committee on Narcotics Abuse and Control, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Select committee file: Hearing Files, Drug Trafficking, 1985 June 05-16 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Select committee file: News Releases, King Assassination, 1977 January (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Select committee file: Petition, Drug Trafficking, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Select committee file: Program, Senior Day `88, 1988 July 29 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Committee on the District of Columbia: Act, D.C. Act 7-19, 1987 May 11 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Committee on the District of Columbia: Calendar, Legislative Calendar Committee of the District of Columbia, 1984-1988 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Committee on the District of Columbia: Manual, Owners Council of the District of Columbia Manual, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Committee on the District of Columbia: Meeting Files, Committee of the District of Columbia, 1971 April 24 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Committee on the District of Columbia: Report, District of Columbia, Committee to the Whole House on the State of the Union, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Committee on the District of Columbia: Rules, Committee Rules, 1987 February 24 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Committee on the District of Columbia: Statement, Appropriations Subcommittee, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Article, "Political Affairs", 1986 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Artifact, Bumper Sticker, "Mend the Crack in the Liberty Bell, D.C. Statehood Now!", 1987 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Artifact, Bumper Sticker, "Washington is a Capital City", undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Award, Howard University, 1983 May 21 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Booklet, "Constitution of the State of New Columbia", 1982 May 29 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Booklet, "Governing the Nation's Capital: Is Statehood the Answer?", 1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Booklet, " The 51st State. Toward Statehood for the District of Columbia", 1984 October (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Booklet, "Analysis of Proposed Constitution of the State of New Columbia", 1986 April (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Booklet, "Statehood for the People of the District of Columbia,", 1986 May (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Campaign Files, Constitution of the State of New Columbia, 1982 May 29 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Campaign Files, Questions Regarding Statehood, undated (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Campaign Files, Quiz about D.C., undated (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Campaign Files, Staff Summary of Findings and Conclusions, undated (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Clippings, D.C. Statehood, 1985-1990 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Clippings, Hobson, Julius W Sr., 1977-1983 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Constitutional Convention, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Kurt Vorndran, 1986 June 11 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Metropolitan Women's Democratic Club of D.C., 1987 January 20 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Phillip Elmore, 1987 March 11 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Edward Moore, 1987 March 11 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Statehood Constitution, 1987 May 12 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, 51 Star Flag, 1987 June 06 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Liberty Train, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Statehood Motorcade, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Support for Statehood (Form Letters), 1987 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Organizations Support for Statehood, 1987-1990 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Correspondence, Requests for Support, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood file: List, Statehood Celebration Honor Certificates Recipient's, 1983 May 21 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood file: List, Statehood Support Committee-Steering Committee Members, 1983 May 21 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood file: List, Whip Swing Lists, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood file: List, Slogans for D.C. Statehood, undated (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Meeting Files, Democratic Caucus Meeting, 1987 May 12 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Meeting Files, Press Briefing, 1987 March 16 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Meeting Files, Subcommittee Hearing, 1987 March 19 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Meeting Files, Executive Committee ACLU Policy Regarding D.C. Statehood, 1988 July 22 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Statehood file: News Releases, D.C. Statehood, 1982-1987 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Statehood file: News Releases, "Mayor Barry Sends Statehood Constitution to U.S. Congress, 1987 September 02 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Statehood file: News Release, "District Officials Call Upon Citizens to Rally on Capital Hill", 1988 July 11 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Proclamation, Statehood Day, 1983 November 02 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Proclamation, Office of the Governor of Maryland on Statehood, 1987 July (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Proposal, Statehood Networking, 1987 March 07 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Proposal, 51 Star Flag of the U.S., undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Report, Hearing on House Resolution 3861, 1984 May 15 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Report, Hearing on Serial No. 99-3, 1985 May 22 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Report, District of Columbia Auditor, 1986 July 30 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Statements, Upon Passage of House Joint Resolution 554, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Statements, D.C. Statehood, 1987-1988 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Statements, D.C. Statehood Constitution, undated (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Statements, Jason Newman in Support of Statehood, undated (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - D.C. Statehood file: Testimony, Edward Ken in Support of Statehood, 1984 May 15 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Brochure, "To Form a More Perfect Union: D.C. Statehood Now!", Circa 1988 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Campaign Files, Member Packet, Fall, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Campaign File, Campaign Schedule, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Campaign Files, D.C. Statehood, Circa 1987 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Campaign Files, House Leadership Support, Circa 1987 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Campaign Files, Lobbying Kits, Circa 1988 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Campaign Files, Sample Editorials, undated (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Correspondence, D.C. Statehood Coalition, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Meeting Files, D.C. Statehood Coalition, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Memorabilia, D.C. Statehood Coalition, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Newsletter, D.C., Statehood Backgrounder, Circa 1987 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Survey, National Awareness and Opinion, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: News Releases, D.C. Statehood Coalition, 1987-1988 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Program, Shape- Up for D.C. Statehood, 1988 March 05 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Proposal, National Coalition for Statehood, 1987 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Statement, D.C. Statehood Coalition, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Statehood Coalition file: Survey, D.C. Statehood, undated (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Organizatioscription, D.C. Statehood Compact Commission, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Campaign Files, D.C. Statehood Compact Commission, 1989 July-August (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Booklet, "If You Favor Freedom", 1986 October (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Campaign Files, D.C. Statehood Compact Commission, undated (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Correspondence, Support Letter, 1983 August 30 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Correspondence, Community Leaders, 1989 September 01 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Directory, D.C. Statehood Compact Commission, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Meeting Files, Conference Delegation, 1988 July (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Meeting Files, Commission Meeting, 1989 July-September (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Plan, National Academy of Public Administration, 1990 July 31 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Plan, Accomplishing The Transition, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Press Kit, D.C. Statehood Compact Commission, 1987 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Press Kit, D.C. Statehood Compact Commission, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Statehood Compact Commission file: Report, Puerto Rico, 1989 September 06 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Announcement, House Resolution 51, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Amendment, House Resolution 51, Circa 1987 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Article, "Draft Response to A Washington Post about Statehood", 1987 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Booklet, "House Resolution 51", 1989 January 03 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Briefing Book, The Caucus of the Democratic Members of the Committee on the District of Columbia, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Briefing Book, House Resolution 51, Circa 1987 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Briefing Book, House Resolution 51, Circa 1987 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Campaign Files, Fact Sheet Chronology of Events in the Pursuit of Full Self Government for WashingtoC., 1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Campaign Files, Statehood Legislative Network, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Campaign Files, March for Statehood, 1989 January 03 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Campaign Files, Victory for D.C., D.C. Statehood Drive Gains Momentum, 1989 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Campaign Files, Co-Sponsor Sheet for House Resolution 51, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Campaign Files, District of Columbia Statehood Celebration, undated (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Clippings, House Resolution 51, 1987-1988 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Correspondence, Freedom Train Participants, 1988 January 07 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Correspondence, Statehood Field Organizers, 1988 March 04 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Correspondence, Support for House Resolution 51, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Correspondence, Romano Mazzoli, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: List. Co-Sponsors of House Resolution 51 in the House of Representatives, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: List, D.C. Statehood Constitutioafting Participants, undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Meeting Files, Strategy and Timetable for D.C. Statehood, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Meeting Files, Statehood Mission Team, 1987-1989 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Meeting Files, Briefing Material and Briefing Book on House Resolution 51, 1988 February (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Meeting Files, Arguments for and Against Statehood, 1988 July 22 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Meeting Files, Briefing Materials on House Resolution 51, 1988 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Meeting Files, Outline and Timetable for D.C. Statehood Campaign, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Meeting Files, D.C. Statehood Issues and Answers, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: News Release, " American Public Shows Strong Support for D.C. Statehood in National-wide Poll", 1988 May 04 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Plan, Plan of Action House Resolution 51, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Proposal, A Comparison of Proposed State Constitution, Circa 1984 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Proposal, Outline House Resolution 51, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Proposal, The Economic Viability of the Proposed State of New Columbia, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Report, Office of Management and Budget on House Resolution 51, 1987 April 22 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Report, New Columbia Admission Act, 1987 September 17 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Report, House Resolution 51, 1987 September 17 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Report, Hearings and Markups on House Resolution 51, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Report, Hearings and Markups on House Resolution 51, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Statements, Coretta Scott King, 1988 January 12 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Statements, D.C. Statehood - Latest Survey Results, 1988 May 04 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Statements, Mark Up of House Resolution 51, undated (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Summary, D.C. Statehood, House Resolution 52, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing 51 file: Transcripts, Radio and TV Inc., 1987-1989 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 325, 1985 January 03 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, Senate 293, 1985 January 21 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 1629, 1987 March 17 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 4776, 1987 September (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 4195, 1990 March 06 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Statehood:Hearing file: Bill, House Resolution 4193, 1990 March 06 (Box 42, Folder 6)